[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":102333,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":261398,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6 </sub>,  you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":11888,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":273287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1456,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":274743,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":[" 5"],"rt":14956,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":289700,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1012,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":290712,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":10547,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":301259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":967,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":302226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4915,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":307142,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1117,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":308259,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the su m is 6 o r bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3753,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":312013,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":993,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":313007,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3739,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":316746,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0 "},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":828,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":317574,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":5945,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":323520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":968,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":324489,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember,  to perfo rm +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3414,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":327904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":842,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":328746,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3518,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":332264,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":760,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":333024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3405,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":336430,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1254,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":337684,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":24216,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":361902,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Simi larly, 3  is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":36439,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":398341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":13691,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":412033,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":983,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":413017,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of a n elemen t is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3316,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":416334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":980,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":417315,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2898,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":420213,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correc t! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1027,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":421240,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3256,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":424498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":864,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":425362,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><b r /> (Re member, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":5901,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":431264,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4167,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":435432,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes","response_history":["yes"],"rt":29508,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":464941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":87402,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":552344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub>  1. Becau se of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":75967,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":628312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":11750,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":640063,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1140,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":641204,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2976,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":644181,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":19071,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":663253,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":41835,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":705089,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":20249,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":725339,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":" No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":10318,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":735657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1164,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":736821,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, non-generators cannot make all numbers.","response_history":["yes, non-generators cannot make all bel","yes, non-generators cannot make all be","yes, non-generators cannot make all b","yes, non-generators cannot make all numbers./","yes, non-generators cannot make all numbers."],"rt":55135,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":791957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":30689,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":822646,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7985,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":830631,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1009,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":831640,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4989,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":836630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3532,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":840162,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6255,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":846417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2850,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":849268,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3819,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":853087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":" add four  to one, get 5, 5 is less than 9 so it is the answer","response_history":["4 =","4 ","4","add four to one, get 5. ","add four to one, get 5.","add four to one, get 5, 5 is less than 9 so it is the answer.","add four to one, get 5, 5 is less than 9 so it is the answer"],"rt":32606,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":885693,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"add 8 to 4 and get 12, 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9 from it, get 3 as the answer","response_history":["add 8 to 3","add 8 to 4 and get 12, 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 0","add 8 to 4 and get 12, 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9 from it.","add 8 to 4 and get 12, 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9 from it, get 3 as the anse","add 8 to 4 and get 12, 12 is greater than 9 so subtract 9 from it, get 3 as the ans wer"],"rt":38667,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":924360,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0 because 0 and 9 will always equal 9","response_history":["0 ","0","9 ","9","0 because 0 and 9 will allways ","0 because 0 and 9 will allways","0 because 0 and 9 will allway","0 because 0 and 9 will allwa","0 because 0 and 9 will allw","0 because 0 and 9 will all","0 because 0 and 9 will always equal 9","0 because 0 and 9 will always equal 9"],"rt":190421,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1114781,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["0","4"],"rt":29339,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1144120,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4235,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1148356,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6 plus 3 equals 9, under +9 that will equal 0","response_history":["6 plus 3 equals 9 w","6 plus 3 equals 9 ","6 plus 3 equals 9, under =9","6 plus 3 equals 9, under =","6 plus 3 equals 9, under +9 that will equal 0","6 plus 3 equals 9, under +9 that will equal 0"],"rt":41325,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1189681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":" Is 2 a g enerator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, because you can't get all numbers with 2","response_history":["no, ","no,","no","n","no, because you can't get all numbers with 2"],"rt":37737,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1227419,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because you can get all number with 3","response_history":["yes, because you can get all nubm","yes, because you can get all nub","yes, because you can get all number with 3"],"rt":29770,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1257189,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in word s how yo u got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, because you can get all numbers","response_history":["yes, because you can get all numbers"],"rt":25013,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1282203,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes, you can get all numbers","response_history":["yes, you can get all numbers"],"rt":21376,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1303579,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and  your ans wers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":15223,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1318803,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +_n 1","response_history":["1 +_n 1"],"rt":60160,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1378964,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"Really not sure, getting lost now.","response_history":["Really not sure, getin","Really not sure, geti","Really not sure, getting lost now."],"rt":13496,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1392461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Don't know.","response_history":["Don't know."],"rt":14773,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1407235,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":6959,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1414195,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7929,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1422125,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":6836,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1428961,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"When I knew n it seemed that way.","response_history":["When I knew n it seemed that way."],"rt":29685,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1458646,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":9404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1468051,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Beyond my ability.","response_history":["Beyond my ability."],"rt":19108,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1487160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<su b>n</sub >, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":1938,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1489099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1881,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1490981,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"37","response_history":["37"],"rt":2459,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1493441,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Di d not gr aduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":2321,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1495763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Calculus, Trig","response_history":["Calculi","Calculsu Trig","Calculus, Trig"],"rt":21143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1516907,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - ne ver heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":8878,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1525786,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":3462,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1529249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3622,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1532872,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3459,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1536332,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2  - somewh at"],"rt":4136,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1540469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":2306,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1542776,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":5455,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1548232,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":7833,"trial_type":" question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1556066,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Interesting, I need more practice. Would like to take some time to freshen up my tired math skills and re-try all of this again!","response_history":["Interesting, I need more practice. Would like to take some time to freshen up my tired math skills and re-try all of this again!"],"rt":32248,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1588315,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]